http://www.super-krete.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Arizona Polymer Flooring (“Company”) has created this privacy policy statement in order to demonstrate our firm’s commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our practices regarding information collection and use solely for the website located at apfepoxy.com (the "Service"). By using or accessing or using the Service, you signify your agreement to be bound by our Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SERVICE.
Personal Information and Aggregate Information:
If you provide it, the Service may collect your name, email address, postal address, telephone number or other information including your resume and associated information. ("Personal Information") In addition, we may also collect non-personally identifiable information, such as IP host address, web pages viewed, browser type, browsing path, and other data, and may aggregate any information collected in a manner which does not identify any individual (“Aggregate Information”).
Information Usage:
We will only use your Personal Information for the purpose it was given to us. We will never sell, trade or rent your Personal Information to any third party not affiliated with Company without your consent except in connection with the sale or merger of Company or the division responsible for such services.
Please note that we reserve the right to access and/or disclose Personal Information and non-personal information we gather as required by law or to the extent necessary for us to investigate suspected fraud, harassment or other violations of any law, rule or regulation, or the Service rules or policies.
Aggregate Information may be shared with any number of parties, provided that such information shall not specifically identify any individuals.
Cookies:
"Cookies" are pieces of information that may be placed on your computer by a website for the purpose of facilitating and enhancing your communication and interaction with that web site. Many websites use cookies for these purposes. We may use cookies to customize your visit to the Service and for other purposes to make your visit more convenient or to enable us to enhance our service. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or flush them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences, in which case you may still use our Service, but it may interfere with some of its functionality. We do not use cookies to automatically retrieve personal information from your computer without your knowledge.
Security:
We cannot guarantee that communications between you and Company or information stored on the Service or our servers, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties such as hackers and your use of the Service demonstrates your assumption of this risk. We have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to perform their duties are authorized to have access to your Personal Information.
Communications with Company:
Any communication or material you transmit to us by electronic mail or otherwise, including any data, questions, comments, suggestions, or the like is, and will be treated as, non-confidential and nonproprietary. Except to the extent expressly covered by our Privacy Policy, anything you transmit or post may be used by us for any purpose, including but not limited to, reproduction, disclosure, transmission, publication, broadcast, posting and/or ranking. Furthermore, you expressly agree that we are free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how, or techniques contained in any communication you send to us without compensation and for any purpose whatsoever, including but not limited to, developing, manufacturing and marketing products and services using such information.
Changes to policy; Opt-Out Process:
We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. However, if at any time in the future we plan to use Personal Information in a way that differs from this policy, we will post such changes here and provide you the opportunity to opt-out of such differing uses. Your continued use of the Service following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept such changes.
All unsubscribe or opt-out requests should be sent to us at contact@apfepoxy.com and we will process your request within a reasonable time after receipt.
Contact: For questions or concerns relating to privacy, we can be contacted at: contact@apfepoxy.com.
United States: Our Service is maintained in the United States. By using the Service, you authorize the export of Personal Information to the United States and its storage and use as specified in this policy.
TOOLBAR
Find a Distributor
Here you will be able to find a distributor from the available states.
Become a Distributor
Love our products? Want to offer high-performance flooring solutions to your customers?
Get Started.
Give Us Feedback
Let us know about your recent customer experience.
Join Our Email List
Get the latest product news, installation techniques and inspiration.
Product Line Card
System Line Card
Open the Door to a World of Opportunities with Exclusive MasterWorks Growth-Driving Programs
CONTACT US:
Arizona Polymer Flooring
4565 W. Watkins St.
CONNECT WITH US ON:
ADMIN:
Login
© 2020 ICP Building Solutions Group.
All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy
